All my brothers, I've now started the science of the heavens
I've silenced the words of my sisters
Hi, so we boarded the cruise ship and we just came into our cabin
This is our cabin and there's...
Hi there
So now we're going to explore the ship and have something to eat and to drink
because we're starving and yeah behind me you can already see the plaza here
which is kind of cool. We just finished our shift for today we handed out the
programs and said hi to everyone boarding ship so now we're going to have
relaxed evening and some drinks probably and here's some cool music
How was the first day people?
What's going on?
I'm just grabbing my stuff and then we go on the water slide.
Water slide!
So this is this year's Cool Girls Who Always Brew.
And now we're off to some watersliding fun.
Open throat, open throat, I will send them
There's no one else but you to blame
How was it?
I lost my lashes!
I'm taking over the cam. I don't know what I'm doing, but we're here at the boat.
You can watch yourself.
Thank you!
So welcome!
So this is the area where all the metalheads are just chilling.
I'm so bad at this!
Yeah, but...
Yeah!
Done!
What are you doing?
I have no idea!
Just filming around.
There's one day that we love being full people and that day is today.
We're hanging out here getting ready for our photo shoot for the calendar for the next year.
We're going to head over to the beach and get some really good shots.
You can see one of our photographers here.
Yeah!
And it's going to be a blast.
We're ready to do some shooting in Bahamas!
Bahama Mama!
Hey, say hi everybody!
That's how good they listen.
So we're at the Bahamas!
Beach time today.
We just did a shoot for the pool girls, for the cruise,
and now free time, chilling and some drinks probably.
What's up YouTube?
We're here on 70k.
She wants her video back.
She wants her camera back guys, but anyway, it was nice to join you guys for a split second. Have a good night
No, I am the love
Are you excited?
Yeah, I'm an Asian.
No.
I'm not.
Whose idea was that again?
Yours?
No, of the water slides.
Water slides.
It escalated quickly.
Phew, gosh.
We're just waiting for Angel because it's late.
Come on.
I'm gonna ask the neighbor.
It's good, right?
I don't like that.
I'm gonna cry.
We're leaving the boat.
Feels like yesterday that I was going that direction.
Let's go!
you